const practiceData = [
  
    {
      "question": "What should be the numerator if 3/7 = []/21",
      "options": ["8","9","3","4"],
      "answer": "9",
    },
    {
      "question": "What should be the numerator if 2/13 = []/65",
      "options": ["10","9","7","20"],
      "answer": "10",
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the missing fraction 7/15 - [] = 2/15 ",
      "options": ["5/15","4/15","8/15","13/15"],
      "answer": "5/15",
    },
    {
      "question": "Find the missing fraction 11/20 - [] = 9/20 ",
      "options": ["15/20","12/20","3/20","2/20"],
      "answer": "2/20",
    },
    {
      "question": "Anil was given 5/8 of basket of apples what fraction of oranges was left in the basket ?",
      "options": ["2/7","3/5","3/8","2/8"],
      "answer": "3/8",
    },
    {
      "question": "Sneha bought 2/5 m of ribbon Sachin bought 3/4 m of ribbon what is the total length of ribbon ?",
      "options": ["5/9","15/20","23/20","20/23"],
      "answer": "23/20",
    },
    {
      "question": "A piece of wire 7/8 m long broke into two pieces one piece 1/4 m long how long is other piece?",
      "options": ["5/8","4/8","6/4","8/12"],
      "answer": "5/8",
    },
    {
      "question": "Out of all the natural numbers from 2 to 15 what fraction of them are prime numbers?",
      "options": ["2/14","7/14","8/14","5/14"],
      "answer": "5/14",
    },
    {
      "question": "Karan has 50 dresses he sold 20 dresses what fraction of dresses are left with him?",
      "options": ["3/5","5/6","4/5","2/5"],
      "answer": "3/5",
    },
    {
      "question": "Subtract 3/4 from 5/6",
      "options": ["1/12","2/12","10/24","8/10"],
      "answer": "1/12",
    },
    {
      "question": "Solve 3 - 15/5",
      "options": ["0","6","12/5","4/5"],
      "answer": "0",
    },
    {
      "question": "Subtract 13/13 - 7/13",
      "options": ["9/13","6/13","13/7","6"],
      "answer": "6/13",
    },
    {
      "question": "Rahul exercised for 1/2 of an hour, Mahi exercised for 3/4 of an hour, Virat exercised for 2/3 of an hour Who exercised for longer?  ",
      "options": ["Rahul","Mahi","Virat","All Same"],
      "answer": "Mahi",
    },
    {
      "question": "If lily read 2/5 of a book containing 100 pages how many pages did she read?",
      "options": ["55","40","10","60"],
      "answer": "40",
    }

];
export default practiceData;